Finding Aid for the Herbert M. Webster Photographs, 1926-1955 MS.3338
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- #391: Hikers on Myrtle Point, Leconte, 1934 March 25; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- #392: Odd tree formation on state line near White Rock, 1934 August 3; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- #393: Unidentified image. Picture [made] by Jim Francis, circa 1928; (Empty) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- #394: White Oak Sinks Near Cades Cove, 1934 January 28; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- #394: White Oak Sinks Near Cades Cove, 1934 January 28; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 17)
- #395: Winter Contrasts. Down Nolands Creed, 1937 November 21; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 18)
- #396: First trip to Greenbrier. Note Chimney in background, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 19)
- #397: Group at Newfound Gap gathering for hike (note construction shed), undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- #398: Trip to Brushy from vacation Camp in Greenbrier. First we saw it raining below us, then we watched the clouds moving in on us. Soon, we were drenched by the heavy rain, 1937 August 17; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 21)
- #399: Rabbit Creek. Tellico Area, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 22)
- #400: Mildred Webster at Bald River Falls, 1934 July 14; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 23)
- #401: Thunderhead from Dry Valley Road, 1935 April 4; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 24)
- #402: Geo. Barber and Friend in the brier patch. Double Springs Gap, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 25)
- #403: Eagle Rocks. State Line after long hard pull up Ramsey Prong to Old Black, destination, Guyot, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 26)
- #404: Sheep on Standing Indian hike, undated; (1 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 27)
- #404: Sheep on Standing Indian hike, undated; (2 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 28)
- #404: Sheep on Standing Indian hike, undated; (3 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 29)
- #405: Site of Halls Cabin near Thunderhead. Only a few stones mark the site. A summer dwelling for herders, bear hunters [-] quarters mecca for hikers, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 30)
- #406: School House. Little Greenbrier. Note that only 5 logs were required to bring wall to proper height, 1955 February; (1 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 31)
- #406: School House. Little Greenbrier. Note that only 5 logs were required to bring wall to proper height, 1955 February; (2 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 32)
- #406: School House. Little Greenbrier. Note that only 5 logs were required to bring wall to proper height, 1955 February; (3 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 33)
- #407: Mildred gets a hand in crossing stream in Tellico Area as Sonny Morris reaches for his camera, just in case, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 34)
- #408: Swimming pool near Greenbrier, 1934 June 23; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 35)
- #409: Harvey Broome. Between Silers & Thunderhead, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 36)
- #410: Group at Moores Spring under crest of Gregory. Sonny Morris on top of big rock. Tom Conner standing center fore ground - Tom Duncan extreme right seated, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- #411: Mildred Webster on Grandfather Mtn., 1934 May 6; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 38)
- #412: Dutch [Roth] on English Mtn., undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 39)
- #413: On Grandfather Mtn. - looking toward Mt. Mitchell, 1934 May 6; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 40)
- #414: Ramsey Cascades. Very Special, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 41)
- #415: Sister Mildred & Catherine Greenlee inside unfinished cabin at Greenbrier, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 42)
- #415: Sister Mildred & Catherine Greenlee inside unfinished cabin at Greenbrier, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 43)
- #416: Platte Balsam's from Mt. Sterling Tower, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 44)
- #417: English Mtn. from Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 45)
- #418: English Mtn. to left background. Greenbrier Pinnacle to right. From Brushy, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 46)
- #419: State Line from Brushy, 1935 June 2; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 47)
- #420: Rainbow Falls [with] Boruff, Kitts, Donaldson, (M) Webster, 1932 August; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 48)
- #421: Rainbow Falls with Maurice, Virgie, John, Clyde, Self, 1932 July; (2 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 49)
- #421: Rainbow Falls with Maurice, Virgie, John, Clyde, Self, 1932 July; (1 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 50)
- #421: Rainbow Falls with Maurice, Virgie, John, Clyde, Self, 1932 July; (3 of 3); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 51)
- #422: Charlies Bunion. From Greenbrier, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 52)
- #423: The Turrentines (Jack & Father). Tom Brightwell at Double Springs Gap. Rare picture - now a wilderness. Spring in Tenn. to left; N.C. to right, 1935 December 15; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 53)
- #424: Dome Falls. Roaring Fork series, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 54)
- #425: State Line trail near Laurel Top. Eastern End, 1936 November 29; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 55)
- #426: State Line trail near Eagle Rock, 1936 November 29; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 56)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (1 of 8); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 57)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (2 of 8); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 58)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (3 of 8); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 59)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (4 of 8); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 60)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (5 of 8); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 61)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (6 of 8); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 62)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (7 of 8); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 63)
- #427: Cascades up stream in Tellico Area, undated; (8 of 8); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 64)
- #428: Ice Overhead! We had to watch for falling ice as well as our footing as we worked our way down the frozen gorge of Roaring Fork, 1940 January 21; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 65)
- #429: Hoffman, Emerson, & Broome taking picture near Silers, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 66)
- #429: Hoffman, Emerson, & Broome taking picture near Silers, undated; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 67)
- #430: Big & Little Huckleberry from trail to Strattons Bald. Trip from the Fain Ranch to Haw Knob, 1934 July 15; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 68)
- #431: Dick Bagwell & the Snake [on] Haw Knob, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 69)
- #432: Unidentified image of interest, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 70)
- #433: Big & Little Huckleberry made from tower on Haw Knob, 1934 July 15; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 71)
- #433: Big & Little Huckleberry made from tower on Haw Knob, 1934 July 15; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 72)
- #434: Rainbow Falls, 1932 August; (1 of 4); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 73)
- #434: Rainbow Falls, 1932 August; (2 of 4); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 74)
- #434: Rainbow Falls, 1932 August; (3 of 4); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 75)
- #434: Rainbow Falls, 1932 August; (4 of 4); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 76)
- #435: Wears Valley, 1955 February; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 77)
- #435: Wears Valley, 1955 February; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 78)
- #436: Standing just outside the opening of the chimney shaft during heavy rain, 1934 June 18; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 79)
- #437: Little Cabin at the Spring - Cherokee Orchard. Destroyed by Park Service, circa 1932; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 80)
- #438: Drinkwater Pool, undated; (Underexposed Negative) (Box 2, Folder 81)
- #439: Unidentified Vista, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 82)
- #440: Leconte trip. Descending wire Cable at Alum Cave. [Departed by] Bear Pen Hollow - return by Alum Cave, 1934 March 25; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 83)
- #441: Unidentified Vista in Snow, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 84)
- #442: Bullhead from trail to Chimneys, 1934 June 10; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 85)
- #443: Old tower on Clingmans Dome, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 86)
- #444: Odd track (trail rounded) in the snow on trip up the Sugarland Ridge. Harvey Broome & I made the discovery, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 87)
- #445: We found this (horizontal) track in the snow on the return from Halls Top, 1936 February 9; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 88)
- #446: CCC Camp near Mt. Sterling P. O. (Walnut Bottoms). Labor Day Trip to White Rock & Mt. Sterling, 1934 September 2; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 89)
- #447: Stream near Chimney Crossing, 1932; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 90)
- #448: Pinnacle from Brushy, 1935 June 2; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 91)
- #449: Silers Bald in the distance. Trip from Clingmans to Silers, 1935 December 15; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 92)
- #450: Looking over brink of Ramsey Cascades to Leconte, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 93)
- #451: Cows near Grandfather Mtn., 1934 June 10; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 94)
- #452: Find Gail! Velma Gail Edmondson (side of Thunderhead), undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 95)
- #453: Rough Crossing! Citico Creek [in the] Tellico Area, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 96)
- #454: Valley at Low Gap on the return from Guyot, 1934 August 3; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 97)
- #455: Major Campbell's Camp [on] Roan Mtn. Benton McKaye, Dutch Roth, Harvey Broome, Grogan, Gail [Edmondson], Lillie Hassis, Guy Frizzell, 1934 May 6; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 98)
- #456: Charlie DuBoise at Eagle Rocks. 22 mile round trip from Newfound Gap - 2"-6" [of] snow, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 99)
- #456: Charlie DuBoise at Eagle Rocks. 22 mile round trip from Newfound Gap - 2"-6" [of] snow, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 100)
- #457: Frozen Head, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 101)
- #458: Grandfather Mtn. Rugged climb, 1934 May 6; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 102)
- #459: Unidentified Vista, undated; (1 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 103)
- #459: Unidentified Vista, undated; (2 of 3); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 104)
- #459: Unidentified Vista, undated; (3 of 3); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 105)
- #460: House Mtn. [with] Mildred W[ebster], Sammy Downey, [and] Tom Brightwell, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 106)
- #461: Charleys Bunion, 1935 August 11; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 107)
- #462: Odd tree formation near Silers [with] Hugh Hoss, 1935 December 15; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 108)
- #463: Citico Creek Crossing. At right, Charlie D. & Prof Duncan give assist to Harriett Foulkes, center, Sonny Morris looks on, as Hugh Hoss gives a hand to Mildred W[ebster], L[eft], & Mildred T., [Right], undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 109)
- #464: Dutch. I know Mary [Frances Dutchess (Watrous) Roth] packed it some where!, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 110)
- #465: Making a fire in the rain. Roger Howell far left, Prof. Duncan crouched to right, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 111)
- #466: Behind a frozen curtain. This picture was snapped by Harvey Broome on hike down Roaring Fork. All falls were frozen. We made entrance behind this fall thru hole at lower right of picture, 1934 February 4; (1 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 112)
- #466: Behind a frozen curtain. This picture was snapped by Harvey Broome on hike down Roaring Fork. All falls were frozen. We made entrance behind this fall thru hole at lower right of picture, 1934 February 4; (2 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 113)
- #466: Behind a frozen curtain. This picture was snapped by Harvey Broome on hike down Roaring Fork. All falls were frozen. We made entrance behind this fall thru hole at lower right of picture, 1934 February 4; (3 of 3); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 114)
- #467: Nances Ferry [in] Grainger County, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 115)
- #468: Old Water Mill near Franklin, N.C., 1935 July 13; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 116)
- #469: A lecture in the Chilhowee [by] Prof. Duncan, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 117)
- #470: Chestnut Hunters on Thunderhead, 1928 October; (1 of 4); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 118)
- #470: Chestnut Hunters on Thunderhead, 1928 October; (2 of 4); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 119)
- #470: Chestnut Hunters on Thunderhead, 1928 October; (3 of 4); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 120)
- #470: Chestnut Hunters on Thunderhead, 1928 October; (4 of 4); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 121)
- #471: Sheep on Thunderhead (Photo by Jim Francis, deceased), undated; (1 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 122)
- #471: Sheep on Thunderhead (Photo by Jim Francis, deceased), undated; (2 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 123)
- #471: Sheep on Thunderhead (Photo by Jim Francis, deceased), undated; (3 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 124)
- #471: Sheep on Thunderhead (Photo by Jim Francis, deceased), undated; (4 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 125)
- #471: Sheep on Thunderhead (Photo by Jim Francis, deceased), undated; (5 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 126)
- #471: Sheep on Thunderhead (Photo by Jim Francis, deceased), undated; (6 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 127)
- #472: Herb & Jim Francis on the Chimneys, undated; (1 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 128)
- #472: Herb & Jim Francis on the Chimneys, undated; (2 of 2); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 129)
- #473: Harvey Broome chopping Blow-down on AT near Messer, N.C., undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 130)
- #474: Boys at Big Chestnut. R. C. [Wallace], Gibbs [Prevast], Wayne T[hompson], 1937 August 17; (1 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 131)
- #474: Boys at Big Chestnut. Wayne T[hompson], 1937 August 17; (2 of 2); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 132)
- #475: Campfire at the Cabin, undated; (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 133)
- #476: Mountain home near Cosby, undated; (1 of 6); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 134)
- #476: Mountain home near Cosby, undated; (2 of 6); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 135)
- #476: Mountain home near Cosby, undated; (3 of 6); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 136)
- #476: Mountain home near Cosby, undated; (4 of 6); (Negative) (Box 2, Folder 137)
- #476: Mountain home near Cosby, undated; (5 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 138)
- #476: Mountain home near Cosby, undated; (6 of 6); (Print) (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Original Negative File Label, undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Original Envelopes, 1926-1955 (bulk 1932-1937) (Box 3)